salesvantage.com 2012-12-30

# SalesVantage.com Privacy Policy Statement

**The SalesVantage.com Privacy Policy**

SalesVantage.com privacy policy represents our commitment to your privacy. This policy discloses what information we gather and how we use it. SalesVantage.com will never sell or rent any personally-identifiable information obtained from a user to a third party. The URL covered under this privacy policy is [www.salesvantage.com](http://www.salesvantage.com/)

Information Gathered

SalesVantage.com gathers information from its advertisers and users in order to offer useful and easily accessible online content and services while providing privacy protection.

**Buyers of SalesVantage.com Advertising:** SalesVantage.com sells online advertising and provides online business content. At the time of ordering advertising, we require personal, business and financial information, such as name, e-mail address, billing address, telephone number and credit card number. This information is necessary to process the order, upload Web links and Ad copy. If you are a repeat customer, you may be asked to update this information. This information is transmitted in 128 bit encryption and we use Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology to protect your online order. Only our order processing and customer service staff has access to your information. We do NOT store or access credit card information from our Web server after your order is processed.

**Submit Your Website Free Offer:** When a SalesVantage.com visitor requests a free "Enhanced Listing" in the SalesVantage.com directory, we require that you provide identifying information including your company name, contact person, telephone number, e-mail address, Website address with company tagline. This information is necessary in order for us to process the request of the "Enhanced Listing" with all the correct information. If the information provided can not be verified or processed correctly we reserve the right to request any additional information necessary to establish and maintain that your company is listed with the correct information. We DO NOT sell or rent any of the information that you submit, the free enhanced listing is permanent with current company ownership; you may cancel your listing at any time by emailing support@salesvantage.com

**Ponders & Principles Subscribers:** SalesVantage.com is a partner with Ponders & Principles LLC and provides a Web link to Ponders free software download. Before downloading the software SalesVantage.com collects personal and business information, such as contact name, job title, company name, telephone number and e-mail address. This contact information is compiled on a separate SalesVantage.com secure database and is only used when a Ponders subscriber requests to upgrade their free service. 

**SalesVantage.com News:** SalesVantage.com e-mails a free double-opt in electronic newsletter to our subscribers weekly; otherwise SalesVantage.com e-mails our subscriber base when it deems it is newsworthy. The registration to subscribe to our Newsletter requires that you give us your e-mail address, job title, industry type and company revenues. We use this information to help us determine type of content, announcements and advertising is the most relevant for the subscriber base. Subscribers may remove themselves anytime from this mailing list by utilizing the unsubscribe option that is clearly noted with an unsubscribe link at the end of each e-mail. SalesVantage.com does not sell its e-mail lists to third parties.

**Get A Quote:** SalesVantage.com provides directory sponsorship advertisers with there own Get A Quote icon. This button links to a Pop-Up form that the prospect fills out personal contact information such as name and email address along with the type of services they are requesting from this specific advertiser / vendor. This information is then electronically forwarded to the advertiser's e-mail address on file. The information is also compiled in a separate SalesVantage.com secure database and is only used when the advertiser requests the information.

Business Relationships

SalesVantage.com provides links to our advertisers Web sites and other business partner Web sites. When you click on those links you are leaving the SalesVantage.com site therefore SalesVantage.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of those sites. You should contact the specific Web sites directly if you have any questions about their privacy policies.

Cookies and Site Tracking

Some parts of the SalesVantage.com site use "cookies." A cookie is an element of data that a Web site sends to your browser, which may then be stored on your computer. The cookies that SalesVantage.com uses do NOT contain any personally-identifiable information. If you do not want cookies sent to your computer, you can set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie. SalesVantage.com is NOT set up to collect or distribute personal information not entered by visitors. The site logs do generate certain kinds of non-identifying usage data, such as the number of hits and visits to the site. This information is used for internal purposes by support and marketing staff only in order to provide quality service and future site enhancements.

Contact Information

If you would like to update or delete any of your contact information, please send an e-mail to support@salesvantage.com. If you have any questions about our privacy practices you may contact the Publisher at jmcmahon@salesvantage.com. Or you may write to the address below. If SalesVantage.com makes any changes to its privacy policy, those changes will be noted on the SalesVantage.com home page and you will have the opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prevent that use. 

SalesVantage.com Inc.  
8432 Broadway Rd  
Wolcott, NY 14590  
Tel: 201.935.3641   
Fax: 315.410.5405 

Policy effective date: July 15, 2003; updated September 18, 2006; updated February 12, 2008

* * *

Copyright © 2000 - 2008 SalesVantage.com, Inc. All rights reserved. 

#### [](http://plus.google.com/b/111268121882645423903/)

#### Sales & Marketing Articles 4U

Advertising & PR   
Advertising, Public Relations

Business Marketing   
Brand Marketing, Direct Marketing, Event Marketing, Incentive Marketing, Marketing Concepts, Marketing Communications

Internet & Web   
Ecommerce, Email Marketing, Internet Marketing, Web Development

Management & Strategy   
Business Etiquette, Executive Coaching, Forecasting & Budgeting, Management Insights, Presentation Skills

Sales & Customer Service   
Distributor Sales, Negotiating, Sales Coaching, Sales Strategy, Selling Tactics, Telemarketing, Time Management

#### Featured Advertisers
